<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Posts on Spaz on Wheels</title>
		<link>https://spazonwheels.com/posts/</link>
		<description>Recent content in Posts on Spaz on Wheels</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 20:52:31 -0500</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="https://spazonwheels.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>The Old Switcheroo</title>
			<link>https://spazonwheels.com/posts/the-old-switcheroo/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 20:52:31 -0500</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://spazonwheels.com/posts/the-old-switcheroo/</guid>
			<description>Back on April 6th, 2019 I made a journey with Road Runner for him to test ride some bikes. I road my 2019 Ultra Limited while he was on his Victory. I ended up going on a test ride at an Indian dealer and four days later ended up picking up a 2019 Indian Chieftain Dark Horse.
So why did I walk away with an Indian when I already own a 2019 Ultra Limited?</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[

<p>Back on April 6th, 2019 I made a journey with Road Runner for him to test ride some bikes. I road my 2019 Ultra Limited while he was on his Victory. I ended up going on a test ride at an Indian dealer and four days later ended up picking up a 2019 Indian Chieftain Dark Horse.</p>

<p><img src="/motorcycles/2019IndianPurchase.jpg" alt="2019 Indian Chieftain Purchase" title="2019 Indian Chieftain Purchase" /></p>

<p>So why did I walk away with an Indian when I already own a 2019 Ultra Limited? Below are a few of my reasons. I still have my Harley but it doesn&rsquo;t get rode as much.</p>

<h2 id="1-the-look">1. The Look</h2>

<p>The color of this bike caught my eye. I&rsquo;ve never seen a bike in a flat bronze before this bike. Roadrunner actually test road the bike I ended up buying and I could not stop thinking about it. I love the styling of the new Indians. I was not a big fan of the previous fairing Indian had, but the new one is definitely my style.</p>

<h2 id="2-handling">2. Handling</h2>

<p>The next thing that got me was the ride. This bike just wants to turn and be leaned. None of my previous bikes liked to be thrown around as much as this one does. It just feels better for some reason. It is very easy to flick around.</p>

<h2 id="3-features">3. Features</h2>

<p>Two features on the Indian really sold me as well. The first is the fact that it comes with power locking bags. To get that in a Harley Davidson you have to fork out extra money and get a CVO. The Dark Horse comes with it standard at a fraction of the price. The second feature which I thought was a gimic was the powered windshield. This is not even an option on any Harley Davidson today. I did not think I would really use it but when you jump on the interstate moving the windshield up is a huge benefit.</p>

<h2 id="4-upgrades">4. Upgrades</h2>

<p>Indian has an amazing upgrade kit called the 116 bore kit. I purchased it with the bike as well as an aftermarket intake, and exhaust. There are options from different Harley Dealers for upgrades like this but they are not manufactured by Harley. The Indian option is designed by them which is awesome. Sure I may do other upgrades in the future but I&rsquo;ve been very impressed with what I currently have. After my custom tune I am running 107 Horsepower and 132 ft-lbs of torque.</p>

<p><img src="/motorcycles/IndianDyno.jpg" alt="Dyno Numbers" title="Indian Dyno Numbers" /></p>

<h2 id="summary">Summary</h2>

<p>I am in love with my Indian and may even get a Chief in the future to have a stripped down bike. My Harley may even leave the stable&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>The Beginning</title>
			<link>https://spazonwheels.com/posts/the-beginning/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 22:26:07 -0500</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://spazonwheels.com/posts/the-beginning/</guid>
			<description>Intro Welcome to Spaz on Wheels. This is the beginning of my blogging regarding my motorcyle adventures. I&amp;rsquo;m not 100% certain where this will go, but figure I&amp;rsquo;ll start putting my thoughts here and post some of my travels as well to share with others.
Background I started riding motorcycles pretty late actually versus some. I got my first bike in 2008 when I was 29 years old. The bike I chose to start with was a 2007 Kawasaki Vulcan 1500cc.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[

<h2 id="intro">Intro</h2>

<p>Welcome to Spaz on Wheels. This is the beginning of my blogging regarding my motorcyle adventures. I&rsquo;m not 100% certain where this will go, but figure I&rsquo;ll start putting my thoughts here and post some of my travels as well to share with others.</p>

<h2 id="background">Background</h2>

<p>I started riding motorcycles pretty late actually versus some. I got my first bike in 2008 when I was 29 years old. The bike I chose to start with was a 2007 Kawasaki Vulcan 1500cc. Probably not the best choice for a starter bike. What stemmed me to get a motorcycle was my father-in-law asking if I&rsquo;d like to ride his Goldwing. I jumped on it with no experience and road up and down the road. After that I went and took the test to get my temps. After getting my temps I purchased the Vulcan. I road it home and forgot my paperwork. So I jumped back on the bike and about two miles from home center striped the bike and laid the bike to the ground. Not the best start to riding but lesson learned.</p>

<p><img src="/motorcycles/2007vulcan.jpg" alt="2007 Vulcan" title="2007 Kawasaki Vulcan" /></p>

<p>After a couple years of riding on my very stripped down Vulcan I transitioned to my first Harley a 2012 Ultra Limited. That is right I don&rsquo;t apparently like to start off small might as well get the biggest bike I can find. This bike served me well and went many miles till I ran the tires out and instead of getting tires I ended up getting a 2014 Ultra Limited to replace it. From there I added parts and raised the handlebars. I did all the work myself which was a first for me. I learned a lot about the bike and how to take it apart and put it back together.</p>

<p><img src="/motorcycles/2012ultralimited.jpg" alt="2012 Limited" title="2012 Harley Ultra Limited" />
<img src="/motorcycles/2014ultralimited.jpg" alt="2014 Limited" title="2014 Harley Ultra Limited" /></p>

<p>At the end of last season I decided to try out the Milwaukee Eight engine. I&rsquo;d heard a lot of good things and decided to pick up a 2019 Harley Davidson Ultra Limited with the 114ci engine. My first impressions where that it had lots more torque. I immediately tore the bike down and started adding parts. This was during the 115th Harley Davidson Anniversary so I got LEDs, Legend Shocks, Tour pack removal kit, and 14&rdquo; handlebars.</p>

<p><img src="/motorcycles/2019ultralimited.jpg" alt="2019 Limited" title="2019 Harley Ultra Limited" /></p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
